Do nothing.
I am in Türkiye
Cara tava Ali de chevas yesterday he is here in Türkiye in Istanbul.
I'm not understanding anything else.
Neither I bro nor I
lie.
There's 1 big car waiting for us here old.
Oi
people
chills that you spill on my back.
Leave me filled with satisfaction when we're done.
action of what's become.
I couldn't Ask for another.
Oh I can't believe it.
I'm even filming already,
right?
Because for us,
we don't lose people.
This one is Joana.
Welcome all good.
As you will be very happy.
And this one?
How is it?
It's okay it's nice to meet you.
All right honey
prepared Guy,
it's still good.
Here Cara otherwise you must.
It's 1 little worried alone it will run more it will
run more it makes 1 really real difference.
So if I came here alone I would be very worried.
He knows?
How are you Nice
To Meet You?
Okay
your time to take off your cap.